Big Sister...
Rah!
We finally meet.
It's been a long time.
Your name is Morse now, right?
Evan Bernstein.
It's been ten years, right, Liese?!
The white lady?
Whenever you're around, it messes me up.
I can't think about anything but you.
Your existence alone screws with me.
So die already!
You did it to spite me, right?
Pretending to be me and keeping House
Bernstein afloat the last ten years.
That's not true, Evan.
I...
I'm ending this here and now.
And then, I shall reach Ākāśa!
For that, I need that Kreuz!
Big Sister!
I'm not letting you have her.
So that's how it is.
You really are always,
always two steps ahead of me!
Maria Bradley.
Since you are here, may I take that to
mean that you have made up your mind?
It's a good opportunity.
Don't worry.
I'm sure there is much you want to say.
After that, let Ray White handle this.
Ray? Why?
There he is.
Ray!
There you are!
The Iceblade Sorcerer
Shall Rule the World
Episode 12
The Boy Who Became the World's Strongest Sorcerer Unveils Ākāśa
Yes. And you're the current Iceblade, right?
And you are the Glutton, Paratrogo.
You know me! What an honor!
You're a sorcerer who eats
other sorcerers' engrams.
I became certain of that earlier.
You've got me all worked up!
This Iceblade will be the best treat!
What the hell is this?
Damn it!
Can't you be quiet for a bit,
you uncultured swine?
There's something important
I need to discuss with him.
What did you say?!
It's nice to meet you, Ray White.
Who are you?
Lieselotte Eden.
Or should I say, the
Sorcerer of Fabrication.
Fabrication...
So you set this all up?
I think Lydia and the others
have an inkling already.
I'll keep it brief.
I am going to make her overheat.
Then I want you to seal it in.
You already have experience with that, right?
Huh?
Chronos Lock.
You're the only one who can do it,
since you're resonating with her.
I'm... resonating with her?
You remember, don't you?
If it is to save her,
I am free to use any method necessary.
That is what my contract with
Bruno Bradley stipulates.
Considering the risks,
you don't seem very concerned.
I've got my own objective.
And for that, I didn't have the
luxury of dismissing any option.
My apologies,
but would you mind taking
care of that loud buffoon?
Rah!
You're pissing me off.
Chronos Lock, release.
Here I come.
I'm going to eat up every last part of you!
So you can readjust on the spot, huh?!
I wouldn't expect anything less.
Liese...
Evan, you get it, don't you?
You cannot reach me.
I don't care anymore!
I don't care!
About Eugenics...
About Ākāśa...
About the Kreuz...
As long as I get to kill
you with these hands!
It seems my voice doesn't reach you, either.
Dark Triad System, activate!
I know all about that, Evan.
A forbidden technique that
stimulates the brain,
thereby amplifying a human's dark side.
The engram temporarily grows
and causes an overheat.
Die!
What is this?!
Prima materia encoding;
material code, material code, decoding,
material code, processing, synesthesia,
embodiment, phenomenon.
Apotheosis.
The destructive factor I possess is
making your engram self-destruct.
It's over, Evan.
Liese!
Is this... the power of the strongest...?
The Sorcerer of Fabrication?
No.
The strongest is the Iceblade.
Ray White is of another caliber.
He exists in a whole different
dimension, you could say.
What?
Suppose there was a sorcerer who
could rule the entire world.
The only one who could do that... is him.
In other words...
The Iceblade Sorcerer shall rule the world.
The Iceblade Sorcerer
Shall Rule the World
Is it all... over?
I can't take this anymore!
We did it!
Even though we couldn't do a single
thing in the Kafka Forest exercise.
That shows how far all of us have come.
And all because of Ray, huh?
Yeah.
We'd never have come this
far if it wasn't for him.
Especially you, Albert.
Right?
Right.
This can't be...
That's...
The same thing as in Kafka Forest?!
Run!
Damn it!
What the...
You all did great!
Sorry we kept you waiting.
You were fighting in your outfits, too!
You're getting top points for this.
We'll be taking it from here.
Let's get rid of the last ones.
The last ones?
What do you mean?
Sorry about that!
These guys were actually all over.
Streams of men who hit on you
and bugs are so annoying.
So ridiculous...
Those seven grand sorcerers...
Right, then.
Let's go, guys!
Carocaro isn't a guy, though.
Yeah, yeah.
Flash of Lightning!
That one is called Lightning Slash.
Febris Draco!
Yamata Orochi!
Is that for real?
I think so.
So it's real, huh?
Right, then!
Can't be losing to my students.
Carol in Wonderland,
Through the Looking Glass!
Go, go, go, go, go, go, go!
We've finally reached the end.
I'm really sad that I have
to say goodbye today,
but Carocaro promises to not forget
all my fans until the day I forget!
Now, please listen to my last song!
Loud-
Kyapi!
What do they mean by "the end"?
You all better get ready!
Icicle Blades!
Ragnarok!
Eat this supreme sorcery!
Jeez. Talk about overkill.
Lydia, you're as violent as ever.
I don't want to hear it from you guys.
I did properly take the surrounding
area into consideration.
As if, you arsonist...
My stage appearance was so moving.
Well...
I have no words.
Wow...
So, Elisa, why are you crying?
Lydia's live sorcery...
As an Ainser, I've been so blessed.
Ray...
Now it's up to you.
Is this all the Iceblade can do?!
Enough talk.
Come at me in earnest now.
Then I won't hold back anymore!
This is my full power!
My original spell that provides
the ultimate body enhancement!
Man-eater!
Ray!
This is your fault.
What?
This is all because you couldn't
open your damn mouth!
The fact that Ray's in that situation,
that I'm like this,
this entire situation!
All because you never talk
about the important things!
I think it's time to eat you now!
Ray!
I'm going to savor you, Iceblade!
Prima materia, encoding,
material code, decoding,
processing, deceleration,
lock,
restoration, compression,
embodiment, picnogram,
material.
What's that?
You want me to crush that, too?
What?
You bastard!
That really hurts!
What?
It didn't break?!
It's over, Paratrogo.
Pandora!
I see.
Now I understand what you are.
Iceblade, you're awesome!
Chronos Lock, activate.
Ray!
Maria...
Let me go. I need to help him.
I told you this is all your fault!
That's like you, always
playing the good girl!
You have it so easy,
not knowing how others feel!
Must be nice.
You stay quiet and look sad,
then everybody around you gets you.
You...
You have no idea what I've been through!
I've suffered so much for you, as well!
You idiot!
You just did that on your own!
I never asked you for any of that!
Because you're always so needlessly caring,
I always get compared to
my wonderful older sister!
And I'm just the failure of a sister!
I have no choice but to always bear it!
Now, and forever!
Why?!
If you're going to be mopey because
you pity me, just cut it out!
It's annoying!
Shut up!
Shut up, shut up!
That's why I hate you.
I hate you!
Pretending to be some heroine in a drama.
You rebel against our parents
and do whatever you want!
I despise you so much, Maria!
Then just say so from the beginning!
That I should disappear!
That you don't need me.
That you wish I'd never been born.
Why would you say that?
I've never wished you hadn't been born.
There're things I don't like about you,
but you are my precious little sister.
I love you.
Big Sister...
Don't say that!
Big Sister! Big Sister!
Maria...
Big Sister!
Was he important to you?
Who knows?
He was seduced by a demon and got jealous.
He had thrown away his humanity.
A foolish man.
Things don't go the way you want.
In reality, that is.
Hurry. Go to her.
What is that?
That's...
Get back!
The overheating is starting.
Maria, stand back and wait.
Please help her.
I will.
Miss Rebecca...
Ray, I said such horrible things to Maria.
You must be so disillusioned with me.
No.
Nobody is free of conflict or worries.
I have so much respect for you.
And...
Maria loves you, too.
Ray...
Chronos Lock.
So both my daughters,
Rebecca and Maria, are safe.
Yes.
The Iceblade, Ray, was the one who did it.
Could you please convey to him my gratitude?
Ray!
Sorry it's me, and not Ray.
Oh, not at all.
But it's almost time for me and Ray to...
Huh?
Wow, you two sure are close.
Not at all.
I'm still not on the same level as you.
Oh, there's no need for modesty.
I'm sorry, but we plan on
spending the night together.
What?
You're just watching fireworks, right?
Oh, no.
I need to properly thank him for today.
I... I showed him my gratitude,
too, after the Magic Chevalier!
And he held me tight and he told me
he wanted us to always be together!
I see, I see.
Well, that sounds like a
wonderful friendship.
But my life is now forever tied to his.
It wouldn't be incorrect to say that
our souls are bound to each other.
You're going to have a hard time.
Ray is very popular with girls.
Quite.
And I do have the capacity
to accept that fact.
In the end, love always wins.
I won't lose.
Neither will I.
You might not think it, but I hate losing.
Why do you two get to have all the fun?
Unfair.
Huh? Hey, what?!
I do have the capacity.
I'm sorry I kept you waiting.
You're all here?
Ray!
It's been a while, Howard.
I'm a student now.
Can you even imagine?
Me, a student.
After having taken so
many lives in the war,
I never thought I would
have the right to be one.
After I lost you back then,
I felt so adrift.
I was so stained in blood that I had
no idea where I could ever fit in.
And it was my master
who showed me the way.
The world that was normal to me was
completely detached from the real world.
Even then,
there were many people who were willing
to accept someone like me anyway.
Howard,
I have friends now!
Amelia Rose
Saeki Iori
Rebecca Bradley
Waki Azumi
You can be happy now, Lydia.
Elisa Griffith
Harumura Nana
Isn't that the Ray you wanted to see?
Yeah.
Claris Cleveland
Hondo Kaede
Lydia's crying!
Evi Armstrong
Umehara Yūichirō
So are you!
Lydia!
Abbie Garnet
Mori Nanako
Dumbpink!
Carol Caroline
Uchida Maaya
Ray!
Lydia Ainsworth
Tanezaki Atsumi
Ray White
Enoki Junya
Man, what a mess.
I've been waiting for you, Ray.
Ariane?
I want you to enter the Magicks War with me!
The Magicks War?
This is so boring!
I hope my big brother comes home soon.